<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Morteza Mousavi</title>
    <link>https://mousavi310.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Morteza Mousavi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 23:05:23 +0430</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mousavi310.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Refreshable SQL Server Configuration Provider for .NET Core</title>
      <link>https://mousavi310.github.io/posts/a-refreshable-sql-server-configuration-provider-for-net-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:04:09 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mousavi310.github.io/posts/a-refreshable-sql-server-configuration-provider-for-net-core/</guid>
      <description>As you know you, there are already configuration providers for a variety of sources. ‌But if you didn&amp;rsquo;t find your source configuration provider, you can simply implement it. It just takes a few minutes to implement a configuration provider. In this blog post, I want to show you how you can implement a custom SQL Server configuration provider and more importantly how you can refresh the configuration data whenever your data in the database changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unique Index With Soft Delete Support in Entity Framework Core</title>
      <link>https://mousavi310.github.io/posts/soft-delete-unique-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 12:24:37 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mousavi310.github.io/posts/soft-delete-unique-index/</guid>
      <description>A unique index on a table field, helps developers to ensure that, their table will not have any duplicated values for that field. On the other hand, a soft delete helps us to logically delete a record while keeping the record itself, using a flag field (for example IsDeleted boolean field) in the table. The problems arise when you want to add a record that its unique indexed field value, has been already used in a deleted record.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://mousavi310.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 23:05:23 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mousavi310.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Hi, My name is Seyed Morteza Mousavi. I am a senior ASP.NET Core developer.
You can find me on
 LinkedIn StackOverflow Github Medium  You can contact me using mousavi310@gmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Blogging!</title>
      <link>https://mousavi310.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 15:55:34 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mousavi310.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi, All. I already published several posts in my medium but I think for some posts that are short and can help some people this is the right place to start.
The area of my posts is not restrict enough but at the beginning I think it is a good Idea to share some of my new understanding in ASP.NET Core with you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>